Norbert Helmuth Mayer - CV

Jobvej 114 3. tv. Grøfthøjparken 166, 8260 Viby J helmuth.norbert@gmail.com 22539447

Personal information

Name: Norbert Helmuth Mayer

Address: Grøfthøjparken 166

8260 Viby J

Phone number: 22539447

Email: helmuth.norbert@gmail.com

Date of birth: 13. May 1987

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/norbert-helmuth-mayer-88229a108/

GitHub: https://github.com/NorbertMayer

Portfolio: https://norbertmayer.github.io/portfolio/

Personal profile

A Web Development graduated student with passion and interest in modern web technologies. With 2 years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and web applications using modern technologies I am ready to enhance the working environment. I am very effective working in a team and working individually. My motivation comes from constantly wanting to improve myself as well as my work, to achieve a solid career.

Work experience

07 January 2019 – 05 April 2019 Intern: Front-end developer at Set Snail

The daily taks were focus on front-end development.

Understanding the VueJS framework architecture by developing different components. Beside VueJS, I worked with FlexBox and SASS to create responsive UI. Through the internship period I had the opportunity to work with two different headless CMS:

Storyblok and Cockpit.

01 February 2017 – 30 April 2017 Intern: Front-end developer for Drupal 7 ecommerce website

at Scandesign Media A/S, design and IT company

The internship was based mostly on understating the functionality of Drupal 7. The mai tasks were to support the other senior developers by testing and fixing the responsiveness issues of the product. I worked on developing responsive layouts for web templates with Bootstrap and CSS.

Norbert Helmuth Mayer - CV

Jobvej 114 3. tv. Grøfthøjparken 166, 8260 Viby J helmuth.norbert@gmail.com 22539447

01 June 2016 – 30 August 2016 Intern: WordPress developer at CartGeneration, digital

marketing agency

Understanding the functionality of WordPress CMS and learning how to develop custom designed websites. Through the internship I had the opportunity to convert PSD mockups for custom WordPress websites. Used of custom post type, custom

field type and third party integration.

Education

January 2018 – June 2019 Erhvervsakademi Aarhus, Web Development Top-up programme

September 2015 – June 2017 Erhvervsakademiet Lillebælt, Odense, Multimedia Design and

Communication

October 2003 – June 2006 West University Vasile Goldis, Baia Mare, Bachelor degree in

Psychology and Educational

Languages

English Fluent in English, both spoken and written

Romanian Native language

Skills

Languages Good knowledge: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, FlexBox

Familiar: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#

Frameworks Good knowledge: Bootstrap, Bulma, Material Design

Familiar: VueJS, Nuxt

Traditional CMS Good knowledge: WordPress

Familiar: Drupal 8, Umbraco

Headless CMS Familiar: StoryBlok, Cockpit

Version control Good knowledge: Git, Jira

Adobe package Good knowledge: Adobe xd